japan-talk.com 2010-12-31

# Japan Talk - Privacy Policy

Tools

  * Member Homepage

Related Articles |   |    

Japan Talk takes your privacy seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. What This Privacy Policy Covers 

This policy covers how Japan Talk treats personal information that Japan Talk collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Japan Talk products and services. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Japan Talk does not own or control, or to people that Japan Talk does not employ or manage. In addition, certain Japan Talk associated companies have their own privacy statements.  Information Collection and Use General 

Japan Talk collects personal information when you register with Japan Talk, when you use Japan Talk products or services, when you visit Japan Talk pages or the pages of certain Japan Talk partners. Japan Talk may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies. When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with Japan Talk and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Japan Talk collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information about your use of products and services that we offer. Japan Talk automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Japan Talk cookie information, and the page you request. Japan Talk uses information for the following general purposes: to customize the advertising and content you see, fulfill your requests for products and services, improve our services, contact you, conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients. 

Children 

Japan Talk does not allow a child under age 18 to register for any Japan Talk services. Japan Talk does not ask a child under age 18 for any personal information. 

Information Sharing and Disclosure 

Japan Talk does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances: We provide the information to trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Japan Talk under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help Japan Talk communicate with you about offers from Japan Talk and our marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to share this information. We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Japan Talk's terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. We transfer information about you if Japan Talk is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, Japan Talk will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. Japan Talk displays targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers (including ad serving companies) may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area. Japan Talk does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. However, by interacting with or viewing an ad you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad. Japan Talk works with vendors, partners, advertisers, and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. 

Cookies 

Japan Talk may set and access Japan Talk cookies on your computer. Japan Talk lets other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other companies' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Japan Talk's cookies. Japan Talk uses web beacons to access Japan Talk cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Japan Talk products and services. 

Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences 

You can edit your Japan Talk Account Information, including your marketing preferences, at any time. New categories of marketing communications may be added to the Marketing Preferences page from time to time. Users who visit this page can opt out of receiving future marketing communications from these new categories or they can unsubscribe by following instructions contained in the messages they receive. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Japan Talk service, such as service announcements, administrative messages and the Japan Talk Newsletter, that are considered part of your Japan Talk account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them. You can delete your Japan Talk account by visiting our Account Deletion page. Please click here to read about information that might possibly remain in our archived records after your account has been deleted. 

Confidentiality and Security 

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. To learn more about security, including the security steps we have taken and security steps you can take, please read Security at Japan Talk. 

Changes to this Privacy Policy 

Japan Talk may update this policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Japan Talk account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. 

Effective Date: June 1, 2004 

|   
People who viewed this also viewed  
---  
   |   | 10 Golden Rules For Japanese Chopstick Manners  |    |    |   | 33 Famous Japanese Snacks   
   |   | Fruits Magazine  |    |    |   | Adventures In Geisha Photography   
   |   | Halloween In Japan  |    |    |   | 10 Ways To Eat Wasabi   
   |   | 10 Golden Rules For Japanese Chopstick Manners  |    |    |   | Pocky Madness   
   |   | Japan Loves Uniforms  |    |    |   | Japanese Street Fashion   
submit link  |   site map  |   search  |   link to us  |   links  |   register  |   about  |   help  |   spam policy  |   privacy  |   terms of service  |   contact us  |   [ Japan Talk in Japanese (beta)   ](http://japanese.japan-talk.com/)   |     
All content on this page is copyright © 2008 Japan Talk.
